["YOU'RE MY FAVORITE SONG"
BY PRINCESS ALIYAH]
[SIKLAB SINGING "UNFORGETTABLE"]
Sometimes I think of you.
The kid is completely drained.
They've been doing nonstop
local tours with Siklab.
I'll still find my way back
to you
[TENSE MUSIC]
- Miguel!
- Miguel.
I know who was behind
the destruction of our resort.
It's my dear sister Serina.
So, it's you.
Angel of Gran Vista Resort.
I'm Serina of
the Montaverde Group of Hotels.
I want your resort
to go bankrupt
so I can buy it
for the Montaverde Empire.
Mama Bebe, Grandfather Xavi,
and I already know
that you were the one
who told those boys
to sabotage our resort.
How dare you?
Why are you picking a fight
with a child?
Why are you taking her side?
You don't even know
what happened.
Why are you being so nice
to that random teenage girl?
Why? Do you miss your daughter
that much?
Young lady.
Are you okay?
Like every other kid,
you see your dead daughter
in that Angel.
I will never stop
until their pathetic
little resort goes bankrupt.
And you can't stop me.
- Serina, where are you going?
- What?
Sir, you need to see this.
Serina, how could you betray me?
We've all played already.
Your turn now.
- And why would I?
- Unless you're intimidated...
by this little lie-detector
gadget.
That's nothing but a toy.
What's the question?
So, Calix, do you have feelings
for Angel?
[INTENSE MUSIC]
["YOU'RE MY FAVORITE SONG"
BY PRINCESS ALIYAH]
What kind of stupid question
is that, Charm?
Of course I don't have feelings
for Angel.
That means you're lying.
So, you like Angel?
Of course not. You know what?
I don't want to play this...
I'm not playing
this stupid game anymore!
I don't like Angel.
I could never like her.
[TENSE MUSIC]
What kind of question was that,
Charm?
You really got him worked up.
He might not let us copy answers
during the exam later.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Boys, wait for me.
So, it's confirmed.
Calix likes Angel.
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
I have a plan, Adie.
I'll make sure Calix
hates Angel forever...
after this.
And what's the plan?
Let's put your hacking skills
to the test.
Time to go, cyber ninja.
Honey, come on.
Give me a ride home.
To the husband who's always
fighting with you?
I'm not about to et her win,
am I?
Why don't you come
with me instead?
Are you serious?
I make a lot of money
at that casino where we met.
I have a lot of connections
there...
influential people...
even some truly ruthless ones.
But I gave all of that up
for you, Serina.
I agreed to be your driver...
because I love you.
Oh, Tyrone.
You know...
if things were that simple...
I'd go with you.
But for now...
this is all I can give you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
You probably thought I wouldn't
be able to track you down?
Enrico?
Enrico...
- it's not what you think.
- Enough. Enough!
You've been deceiving me
for so long.
No. That's not true.
What do you mean it's not?
There you go.
That's what you're good at...
gaslighting people.
Twisting all of your mistakes
around...
and making me feel like
I'm the one who's wrong.
What are you talking about?
There.
That bracelet he's wearing.
Right?
I suspected something about it,
but you told me it was nothing.
You got so defensive,
didn't you?
That bracelet Tyrone
is wearing...
you gave it to him, didn't you?
You bought it from Roxanne?
He just asked me to buy it
for him.
Tyrone has a girlfriend
in the U.S.,
an old hag who gives him money
whom he met at a casino.
Despite everything that I did,
you have the nerve to accuse me
of having an affair?
But it turns out...
- you're having an affair...
- Enrico, you're wrong.
- You're wrong.
- What's wrong about it?
Enough!
Tyrone, you're fired.
And I'll make sure...
that no one hires you
for any job...
anywhere in Solmera City.
And you, Serina...
you'll never set foot again
in my home.
No, no...
And from now on, my lawyer will
be the one speaking to you
regarding our annulment.
What? What annulment?
What annulment? Enrico, please!
Please, Enrico!
Enrico!
Idiot! This is all your fault.
You're such an idiot!
We got caught because of you!
What was I supposed to do?
We already got caught.
No, this can't happen.
I can't just lose everything
I've worked so hard for.
I can't become poor again.
What are you going to do?
You said...
You said there was someone
who could take care of Enrico?
Right?
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
I wish you had never
disappeared, Isabella.
I wish I had never opened
my heart again.
I wish I had never fallen
in love with Serina.
Now that we're no longer
together...
I'll focus on finding
our princess.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
As long as I'm alive...
I'll never stop searching
for you, my child.
I won't give up.
Even if so many people say that
you're already dead.
[TIME BOMB TICKING]
[EXPLOSION]
[GRIPPING MUSIC]
So, Doc, what did you find?
Why did my son collapse
the other day?
Neil, I found lesions
on your son's vocal cords.
This is commonly seen in singers
who are severely overworked.
I think what Miguel needs
right now
is at least six months of rest.
Otherwise, his singing voice
could suffer permanent damage.
Six months?
Doc, six months isn't possible.
My son has too many commitments.
Siklab has a world tour.
Surely we can manage this
with medication,
treatment, therapy,
or something.
Dad, didn't you hear
what the doctor said?
I need to rest.
I'm sure my fans
will understand.
No, they won't.
You know, Miguel,
you're partly to blame
for this too.
Instead of resting,
you keep busking.
And now, you'll be gone
for six months.
Do you know how long six months
is in this industry?
People will forget you.
Siklab is at its peak right now
and you're going to step away?
What are you thinking?
[CELLPHONE RINGS]
Hello, Randel.
Contact our international
tour teams.
- I just need some air.
- If Miguel has to lip-sync
- so this tour can continue...
- I'm going to do some busking.
- then that's what we'll do.
- Take me there.
As long as this tour goes ahead.
Yes.
Miguel...
Miguel, where are...
Miguel!
Oh, Zion.
["FIRST LOVE" INSTRUMENTAL]
It's beautiful.
Your crown looks beautiful.
It suits you perfectly.
Good thing the online seller
responded quickly.
At least we got it, right?
Let me see.
Thank you.
Shall we start?
Sure, let's do it.
Okay.
Glasses don't really work
for a prince.
Here, sit down.
Right here.
There.
Angel, I can't see
without those.
You won't need them anymore.
What's that?
Remember when I asked you
about your prescription
the other night?
I bought it for you.
For me?
Yes.
It's my way of repaying you
for everything you've done
for me.
You know, at my old school,
I didn't really have
many friends because...
they said I was a nerd.
You're the first person
I've ever become this close to.
Look up.
There.
Oh, see?
They suit you much better.
You look cuter.
Cuter?
Cute enough for Charm
to notice you.
Weren't you planning to ask her
to the Siklab concert?
After all, you still
have the tickets.
Mr. Moon never claimed them
anyway.
Oh, right.
I really hope she says yes,
Angel.
She'll definitely say yes.
Thank you so much.
Here you go!
- Matcha for energy!
- Of course.
So, how's it going?
Well, I hacked
into the campus CCTV,
and I got the footage
from when we were playing
the lie detector game.
Oh, my gosh. Let me see.
- Now using AI...
- Yeah.
I edited it to make it look like
Calix is admitting
that he likes Angel.
- Want to see it?
- Show me.
[ADIE CHUCKLES]
Do you have feelings for Angel?
What kind of stupid
question is that, Charm?
Of course I do.
[BOTH LAUGH]
- Oh, my gosh.
- See that?
See? It even has subtitles.
Now, the next step is,
I'll post this in our group chat
for Section Narra
for everyone to see
using Angel's account.
No way you pulled that off.
I mean, it's not that hard.
She logged into Brighton's
public Wi-Fi.
Do it.
Start the chaos.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[TENSE MUSIC]
Ah, wait a second. I'll put
my phone on Do Not Disturb...
so there won't be any
notifications...
- okay?
- Okay.
Then...
I'll place it right here.
There.
- Ready?
- Okay, let's do it.
Lights, camera...
- action!
- Action!
Okay, wait a second.
["FIRST LOVE" INSTRUMENTAL]
I never thought
you would find me, my prince.
I thought I would be alone
forever.
Thank you for coming.
This is so cheesy.
Why do we even have to act out
what our classmates wrote?
Who even wrote this?
Poncy and Dash wrote it.
Ah, that explains why
it's so bad.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Okay, take two, take two.
All right, take two, take two.
Okay, take two!
- Take two.
Okay.
I never thought you would
find me, my Prince.
[SOFT ROMANTIC MUSIC]
I thought I would be alone
forever.
Thank you for coming.
From...
the very first time I saw you,
Princess...
I knew...
I immediately felt something
different.
And that's because...
I love...
[STAMMERS]
Did you forget your line?
No, no.
What's your line again?
What's written here?
It's such an easy line.
You just have to say
you love me.
There it is.
Oh, right.
That's your line.
Do you want to read it?
[TENSE MUSIC]
Hey!
Wait, the...
- Wait, my phone.
- So this is where you've been!
What are you doing here?
You're asking me? Seriously?
After what you did?
Look at her, acting like
she knows nothing.
- Oh, here.
- You're in trouble now.
Do you have feelings for Angel?
You posted this
in our Section Narra group chat.
- Of course I do.
- Enough, Raviel!
I didn't post that.
I know nothing about it.
You hacked the classroom CCTV,
edited the video...
to make it look like what?
That I like you?
How dare you make a fool of me,
Angel?
As if I'd ever fall for someone
like you.
Calix, can you please calm down?
Angel and I have been together
all day.
So how could she have uploaded
that?
And...
we didn't even know about
your lie detector game.
Shut up, Zion!
For all I know,
you're part of this too.
Angel is really smart,
isn't she?
I'm sure she's smart enough
to come up with all of this...
just to humiliate me.
You're smart too, Calix.
You know I couldn't do something
like that.
Wouldn't you?
You have every reason
to do this to me, Angel.
Stop denying it.
Let's go, Calix.
We'll take care of Zion.
You handle Angel.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You're done for.
- Look how angry he is.
- Angel, come on.
She really got under his skin.
All right, boys, get Zion.
- What are you doing?
- Hey!
- Angel, come on!
Go after them!
My eye!
- Chase them!
- You're dead, Zion!
Hey! Go after them, hurry!
[GRIPPING MUSIC]
[LINE RINGING]
You know, I've been calling
and messaging Sir Enrico
for a while now,
but I still can't reach him.
His important guest
is about to arrive.
The...
The Japanese detective who's
searching for his daughter.
Mr. Niro.
I asked Sir Enrico
if he wanted me to accompany him
on his yacht,
but he said he wanted
to be alone.
You know, Sir Enrico
isn't the type to forget
an important appointment.
I have a bad feeling about this.
What's going on?
- Sir Enrico has a guest...
- Gino!
Gino...
Sorry. That's supposed
to be a secret.
Gino, please take this child
to the quarters first.
I'll still try to check
on Sir Enrico at the port.
Okay, okay.
I hate secrets in my house.
And I hate it when people talk
behind my back.
Ma'am Serina...
I just told Gino
to have Sir Enrico's personal
chef come tomorrow.
Excuse me, Miss Serina.
The police are here.
They have something to tell you
about Sir Enrico.
What about my husband?
We received a report
that the yacht
belonging to Mr. Enrico
Montaverde exploded.
We're currently searching
for him.
What? What did you say?
My husband's yacht exploded?
Wait, wait.
- Ma'am, Ma'am.
- Enrico, no, no.
- That can't have happened.
- Get some water. Hurry.
- Enrico.
Ma'am...
Wait a minute.
How did that happen?
Sir Enrico has always
used that yacht.
The investigation
is still ongoing.
Right now, we're looking
into the possibility
of a gas leak or engine failure.
The search and rescue operation
is also ongoing.
Oh, my god. Oh, my god!
No, no, no.
Please, please do everything
you can to find him.
Yes, Ma'am.
Oh, my god.
- Enrico.
- Where's the water?
- Where is the water?
- We'll be going now.
This can't be happening.
Ma'am.
[SERINA SOBBING]
Ma'am, please
have some water.
Ma'am. Ma'am.
Ma'am, please calm down.
Ma'am, I'll take care of that.
Coming this Monday
on You're My Favorite Song...
Let's split up.
I'll drop you off at the corner
then I'll take care of throwing
them off our trail, okay?
The news has already reported
Enrico Montaverde's death
as an accident.
That's Serina's husband.
Did these police officers
kill him?
[PANTING]
Oh, no. Someone's here.
Could that be Calix?
I need to get out of here.
Is somebody there?
["YOU'RE MY FAVORITE SONG"
INSTRUMENTAL]
Frenny!
This is unbelievable.
What did it say?
Your horoscope
says you'll meet a man
who will make your heart race!
Frenny!
[SQUEALS]
This is so exciting.
Frenny.
- What?
- Enrico?
Enrico Montaverde?
You're right.
["YOU'RE MY FAVORITE SONG"
INSTRUMENTAL]